think the first factor we have to recognize here is that a nuclear armed, you know, serial killer
masquerading as a nation state with the full backing of the United States has failed to impose
a surrender on Palestinians wearing, you know, Adidas flip-flops, track suits, and operating with
largely domestically manufactured weapons. When I watch Palestinians, I can't help but think about
the Middle Passage. And again, it's not to say that there aren't other people that are going
through terrible things. We always talk about the people, the Rohingya, we talk about the Ayers,
we talk about Sudan, we talk about Congo. It's just that we get to physically see in Palestine
what they're like going through. So they say the roughly 10% of people who survived the Middle
Passage of the transatlantic slave trade make up, you know, those of us who are descendants,
like they are our DNA. And if you survived that, then you have a particular strong, like visage
and countenance. So like, when you see the black people of the United States, and you're like, damn,
like, they just be running. And you know, the reason why we have all of this medical racism is
because there's this idea that like, we are immune to pain. And it's not that we're immune to pain.
We just strong as a motherfucker because we came from the strongest motherfucker of the folks we came
from. So when I see Palestinians, and their ability to continue to sustain and maintain not only their
faith, but even just carrying on, knowing that a lot of us can't even handle a breakup. We in a pool
on the ground, because somebody don't like us. I see that. And I'm like, these are descendants.
They're literally the descendants of folks who are going through it. And their DNA is like
fortifying itself over time. And you know, these Zionists, they always say like, oh,
everybody in, in Palestine is a terrorist and we have to kill the children because they'll grow up
and be terrorists. No, there's, there's no proof to suggest that that would be the case because they
are the gen, they are from generations of those who came before and not everybody has grown up to be a
resistance fighter. That being said, they continue to be strong. They have been attacking these people
nonstop, but in the last two years, in so many ways, all at once. And they maintain. And I know
that's so annoying to them Zayos. And they're going to continue to maintain. The indigenous people of the
nations that were genocided by the likes of Christopher Columbus and conquistadors, et cetera,
they simply had no way out. Oftentimes they were on islands or they were, you know, jungle locked in
ways that they couldn't escape. However, what we have seen is that the native Americans of the United
States, in many cases, you know, of Canada, et cetera, like the indigenous people, even the Mayans,
they're still here. They're still here. And I believe that there's, there's like a, a force that
will awaken. And Palestine and Chassa awakened that in so many of us. May the force be with you.
Inshallah.